

CONTACT ME AT

harrietrsthompson@gmail.com



https://hazthompson.github.io



harriet-thompson-32925663/

SKILL STACK

- React
- GraphQL & Apollo
- Node.is
- css
- Ruby on rails
- Angular
- Cypress Testing
- MongoDB
- PostgreSQL
- Flutter

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Tylt - tylt.app

An app that makes it easier to keep track of and share the recommendations we get from friends every day.

React, Ruby on rails, GraphQL, Material UI

Soundtrip - soundtrip.app
Search live music events in
your area and generate these
as a Spotify playlist.
React, Ruby on rails, GraphQL

HARRIET THOMPSON

WEB DEVELOPER

I'm a hard-working web developer with 2 years of full stack experience. I enjoy working in a diverse team and pride myself on being a fast learner with a flexible attitude. I strive to work in an environment that promotes creativity and innovation. I am looking to be part of a talented team that works together to build something they really care about.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Junior Full Stack Developer

Digital Lab at BC Children's Hospital | Jan 2020 - Apr 2021

- Project lead for Seizure Action Plan app built in React/Node.js/graphQL/MongoDB with Cypress tests. This app provides an online database for healthcare professionals and a patient facing website outlining steps to take when a patient is having a seizure.
- Training and mentoring new interns.
- · Working with both Rest API and GraphQL.
- Working across numerous projects, gaining knowledge other in languages and frameworks such as Python, Angular and Jest testing.

Web Developer Intern

Digital Lab at BC Children's Hospital | Aug 2019 - Dec 2019

- worked primarily on a data visualization app built with React, D3 and anime JS. This sharpened my knowledge of React, SVGs, animations and charting libraries.
- Day to day bug fixes both front-end and back-end.
- Built confidence in git best practices

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Web Development Bootcamp

Lighthouse Labs | Apr 2019 - Jul 2019

A full-time bootcamp, covering topics including javascript, Node.js, React, Ruby, MongoDB and PostgreSQL.

University of Durham

Combined Honours in History & English Literature | Oct 2009 - Jun 2012 | 2:1